Do you hear the people sing? Singing the song of angry men. It is the music of the
你聽到人民在唱嗎？唱著憤怒人民的歌。這是
people who will not be slaves again. When the beating of your heart echoes the beating
不再為奴的人民的歌。當你的心跳呼應著鼓聲
of the drums. There is a life about to start when tomorrow comes.
當明天來臨時 嶄新生活即將展開
Will you join in our crusade? Will you be strong and stand with me?
你願加入我們的聖戰嗎？你能堅強與我並肩嗎？
Beyond the barricade, is there a world you long to see?
在路障之外 有你想看的世界嗎？
Then join in the fight that will give you the right to be free.
加入這場戰鬥吧 讓你獲得自由的權利
Do you hear the people sing? Sing the song of angry men.
你聽到人民在唱嗎？唱著憤怒人民的歌
It is the music of the people who will not be saved again.
這是不再被奴役的人民之歌
When the beating of your heart echoes the beating of the drums.
當你的心跳呼應著鼓聲
There is a life about to start with tomorrow night.
有嶄新生活即將隨明夜展開
Will you give all you can give So that the bad and the bad are lost?
你願傾盡所有 讓邪惡都消失嗎？
So those poor and soft will live Will you stand up and take your chance?
讓弱小者得以存活 你願站起來把握機會嗎？
The blood of the martyrs Will fall to the meadows of Christ
烈士的鮮血將灑落在 Christ 的草原
Do you hear the people say Sing a song for man we know?
你聽到人民說嗎？為我們認識的人唱首歌
This is the bluesing of a people who will not be slaves again.
這是不再為奴的人民之歌
And the beating of your heart echoes the beating of the drums.
你的心跳呼應著鼓聲
There is a life around which nothing tomorrow comes.
明天將帶來嶄新生活
Halt!
停！
Drop!
放下！
No, no, no!
不 不 不！
No!
不！
He's an innocent woman!
她是無辜的女人！
Let her out!
放她出來！
Come on!
拜託！
Watch him for the right!
盯著他以防萬一！
Thank you, sir.
謝謝你 先生
Thank you, monsieur.
To the barricades!
到路障去！
Leave La Proge!
離開 La Proge！
Come on!
拜託！
Come on, Joe!
拜託 Joe！
Come on, get down, get down!
來 蹲下 蹲下！
Move out, move out, move out!
前進 前進 前進！
Come on, get off your arse, it's begun.
來 動起來 開始了
I'm sorry, pal.
對不起 朋友
Thank you.
謝謝
I'm sorry, I'm going to get turned.
對不起 我要走了
Ah, sorry.
啊 抱歉
We need as much furniture as you can throw a dime!
我們需要你能搬的所有家具！
Throw everything you have!
把你有的全部扔出來！
Wait! No! Wait!
等！不！等！
Watch yourself! Watch yourself!
小心點！小心點！
Oh, my God!
噢 我的天！
I need a volunteer, someone who can find out their plan and when they will attack.
我需要志願者 能找出他們計劃何時進攻的人
I can find out the truth, I know their ways, fought their wars, served my time, in the
我能找出真相 我認識他們的手段 打過仗 服役過 在
days of my youth.
在我年輕的歲月裡
See the people unite!
看人民團結起來！
I pray you're right.
我祈求你是對的
Dogs will pack.
狼群會聚集
Please don't bite!
拜託不要咬！
It will do what it strikes!
它會做它該做的！
Red, the blood of angry men
紅 憤怒人民的血
Black, the dark of ages past
黑 過去時代的黑暗
Red, a world about to dawn Black, the night that ends at dawn
紅 即將破曉的世界 黑 終結於黎明的夜晚